

Profile

2 years of experience in IT industry.

I have implemented 4 software projects, working on coding, testing, issues detection, analysis and resolving, code improvement.

Good understanding of the OOP and design patterns.

Most of my technological expertise lies in the area of web technologies, JavaScript, HTML/CSS, TypeScript, ReactJS.

I have experience with Agile, Scrum.

Employment History

Frontend Developer at SharpMinds, Chernivtsi

September 2018 — August 2019

Developed a frontend part of the software for creating CRM, project management, document management.

On this project I created:

- control for viewing and creating meetings using KnockoutJS, MomentJS, Less;
- relationship model for business processes using JointJS, Rappid, KnockoutJS, Less;
- · dashboards, forms, markup.

Frontend Developer at Elogic, Chernivtsi

November 2017 — September 2018

- worked on frontend part of Magento 2 projects using KnockoutJs, RequireJS, Gulp, Less;
- developed markups for Magento progects;

Frontend Developer at Boost Solutions, Chernivtsi

February 2017 — August 2017

- created user interfaces using HTML/CSS, Less, JQuery;
- developed admin panels and dashboards using AngularJs, Firebase, Bootstrap.

Education

Master's degree, Chernivci National 'Juriy Fedkovyc' University, Chernivtsi

September 2016 — January 2018

Applied Math

Bachelor's degree, Chernivci National 'Juriy Fedkovyc' University, Chernivtsi

September 2012 — May 2016

Applied Math

Details

Brussels, Belgium, +32456163048 katerina.holodna@gmail.com

Links

GitHub LinkedIn

Skills

HTML/CSS

JavaScript

ReactJS

Redux

LESS, SASS

KnockoutJS

jQuery

Bootstrap

TypeScript

Firebase

Webpack

Git

Languages

English

Russian

Ukrainian